Who is that kicking Hei Wuya so hard?
His name is Huo Yi.
He's my best friend.
Bai,
who hurt you like this?
Qiongqi.
No,
it was Feng Qingwu.
Qiongqi went berserk
because she controlled him.
Huo Yi,
here.
Throw Hei Wuya down the cold pool.
Tell that guy
that Hei Wuya injured Bai,
and he can do whatever he wants with him.
The cold pool.
Finally,
a chance.
Ever since I saw that eye,
I knew there must be a secret
at the bottom of the cold pool.
Uncle, you finally let it slip.
There really is something fishy
at the bottom of the cold pool.
I want you to take me to see it.
There's actually a stone door here.
Stop hitting me!
I really didn't hurt Bai!
Still trying to argue?
I'll beat you to death!
Tengshe,
you brat,
you still dare to come down and find me?
How is Bai doing now?
Why does my heart hurt so much
when I see this Tengshe?
I had a strange feeling
when I saw Chilian back then too.
Could my background
be related to snakes?
Girl,
what's wrong?
It hurts.
My heart hurts so much.
Answer me,
how is Bai?
He's fine.
You don't need to worry.
As for this Hei Wuya,
consider him a toy for you.
Just don't play him to death.
I have things to do, I'm leaving.
Who is she?
What is that brat doing?
Feng,
lock her in the dungeon.
Send her to Qilin Mountain
on a chosen day.
Master Wu, please.
Since you are one of
the Ten Masters of Yanmen,
I won't put shackles on you.
It's all this wild girl's fault.
Let me go! I'm going to kill her!
Madam, I'm sorry.
You can punish me however you want.
Oh, no, no, no.
Feng Qingwu controlled you.
I believe Bai won't blame you either.
Now is not the time to talk about this.
Sect Leader, we are in a mess ourselves.
It would be terrible if the Demonic Cult
took advantage of the situation.
And with the current situation,
our enemies are not only the Demonic Cult.
Alliance.
These days,
I've learned a lot
about the outside world.
If Yanmen, Buerkai,
and Sanzangwu can form an alliance,
the Demonic Cult won't dare
to cause trouble again.
But we don't have any ties with Buerkai.
Nor with Sanzangwu.
Okay,
girl.
Take Huo Yi and Qiong Qi
to facilitate the alliance.
Three days.
If the alliance isn't formed
within three days,
I will go find Yu Qitian myself.
Understood.
My Lady,
this is where Bu'erkai is hidden.
why do you look so unhappy?
Uncle only gave us three days.
But right now,
I don't even know where Yu Qitian,
the leader of Bu'erkai, is.
You don't need to worry about that,
My Lady.
I can find him.
Who goes there?
I am A'kong.
Is this Yu Qitian?
No,
this is Jiao Tu,
the accountant of Bu'erkai.
The real Yu Qitian
is behind this screen.
A'kong.